Cayce Family Collection
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
- Hugh Lynn Cayce, 1907 1982
  - Personal, 1931 1982
    - Box 21D, audiocassettes (see coll. 1, 21C boxlist)
  - Professional, 1935 1982
    - Box 22
      - building plans [A.R.E. headquarters], 1944; Folder 22:1
      - calendar, 1975 1977; Folder 22:2
      - correspondence [A.R.E. criticism], 1962 1979; Folder 22:3
      - correspondence [Maxine Asher] Ancient Mediterranean Research Association, 1973 1977; Folder 22:4
      - correspondence [Marcus Bach], 1966; Folder 22:5
      - correspondence [Hereward Carrington], 1938; Folder 22:6
      - correspondence [Julia Chandler], 1944 1945; Folder 22:7
      - correspondence [Ethel Clyde], 1944; Folder 22:8
      - correspondence [Cosmic Awareness, Inc.], 1967 1979; Folder 22:12
      - correspondence [Edgar Cayce Foundation readings indexing project], 1962 1964; Folder 22:13
    - Box 23
      - correspondence [Edgar Cayce's 100th Birthday Celebration in Hopkinsville, Kentucky], 1977; Folder 23:1
      - correspondence [John Seaman Garns] School of Psychology and Divine Science, 1943; Folder 23:2
      - correspondence [Garvey Foundation], 1971; Folder 23:3
      - correspondence [Gilberto C. Girardo] Edgar Cayce comic book, 1971; Folder 23:4
      - correspondence [homosexuality], 1968 1980; Folder 23:5
      - correspondence [inquiries about A.R.E.], 1966 1977; Folder 23:6
      - correspondence [Tom Johnson] Heritage Market, 1976 1979; Folder 23:7
      - correspondence [Renee Kessler], 1964 1965; Folder 23:8
      - correspondence [lectures to community organizations], 1967 1980; Folder 23:9
      - correspondence [lectures to religious organizations], 1967 1973; Folder 23:10
      - correspondence [Dan McDougald, Jr.] Yonan Codex / Khabouris Manuscript, 1975 1999; Folder 23:11
      - correspondence [Norfolk Testing Laboratories, Inc.], 1981; Folder 23:12
      - correspondence [Phil Osol], 1968 1974; Folder 23:13
      - correspondence [Will Oursler], 1969 1971; Folder 23:14
      - correspondence [personal guidance], 1971 1981; Folder 23:15
    - Box 24
      - correspondence [Inga Price], 1970 1975; Folder 24:1
      - correspondence [professional] N, 1964 1980; Folder 24:2
      - correspondence [professional] P, 1957 1981; Folder 24:3
      - correspondence [professional] R, 1963 1974; Folder 24:4
      - correspondence [professional] S, 1966 1982; Folder 24:5
      - correspondence [Mae Gimbert St. Clair to Thomas Sugrue], 1944; Folder 24:5a
      - correspondence [professional] T, 1968 1980; Folder 24:6
      - correspondence [professional] U, 1974 1980; Folder 24:7
      - correspondence [professional] V, 1961 1982; Folder 24:8
      - correspondence [professional] W-Z, 1968 1977; Folder 24:9
      - correspondence [Radioactive Appliance], 1960 1964; Folder 24:10
      - correspondence [T. Lobsang Rampa], 1971 1975; Folder 24:11
      - correspondence [Morgan Delar Rayburn], 1970 1974; Folder 24:12
      - correspondence [Leona Ringle], 1960 1975; Folder 24:13
    - Box 25
      - correspondence [John Rossner] International Institute of Integral Human Science, 1974 1978; Folder 25:1
      - correspondence [spiritual questions], 1967 1981; Folder 25:2
      - correspondence [student lectures and research], 1961 1973; Folder 25:3
      - correspondence [John Sutton] appliances, 1963 1965; Folder 25:4
      - correspondence [Grethe Tedrick], 1977 1982; Folder 25:5
      - correspondence [Wet Cell Appliance], 1956 1971; Folder 25:6
      - correspondence [youth], 1970 1971; Folder 25:7
      - drafts [essays on Edgar Cayce], undated; Folder 25:8
      - ephemera [Glad Helpers Prayer Group], 1941 1979; Folder 25:9
      - essay [early Association for Research and Enlightenment and Atlantic University], 1940; Folder 25:10
      - interview [The Edgar Cayce Legacy], 1971; Folder 25:11
    - Box 26
      - lectures [bound book], 1935 1964; Folder 26:1
      - lecture materials [Health and Healing Workshop], 1982; Folder 26:2
      - lecture notes [Egyptian History; Egypt's Influence on the Present; The Action of Grace In Your Life; Reincarnation; All Things to Your Remembrance; Project X; The Secret Place of the Most High; The Challenge of a Modern Seer; Strange Powers of the Mind; The Vine and the Branches], 1940 1960; Folder 26:3
      - lecture notes, 1944 1978; Folder 26:4
      - lecture notes [Chinese and Christian Meditation], undated; Folder 26:5
      - lecture notes [Understanding Self: The Key to Spiritual Growth], 1948; Folder 26:6
      - lecture notes [Whom Are You Creating?], undated; Folder 26:7
      - lecture publicity materials, 1950 1972; Folder 26:8
      - lecture [Roanoke College], 1969; Folder 26:9
      - lecture schedules, 1971; Folder 26:10
      - lecture tour and Egypt trip materials, 1962 1963; Folder 26:11
      - play program [The Freak], 1981; Folder 26:12
      - proposal [Preservation of the Edgar Cayce Readings] Edgar Cayce Foundation, undated; Folder 26:13
      - proposal [System Proposal: Edgar Cayce Foundation] Wang Laboratories, 1976; Folder 26:14
    - Box 27
      - readings extracts [Eighth Annual A.R.E. Congress], 1939; Folder 27:1
      - real estate records, 1946 1954; Folder 27:2
      - report [Application for a Grant in Support of Construction of the A.R.E. Library], 1974; Folder 27:3
      - report [First Spiritual Healing Seminar: Wainwright House], 1953; Folder 27:4
      - reports [Second and Third Spiritual Healing Seminar: Wainwright House], 1954; Folder 27:5
      - reports [Fourth and Fifth Spiritual Healing Seminar: Wainwright House], 1955 1956; Folder 27:6
      - report [Progress Report: Commission for the Study of Spiritual Healing], 1953 1957; Folder 27:7
      - report [Proposal for Research on the Hyperactive Child Syndrome], 1973; Folder 27:8
      - report [Selections from the Readings Given by Edgar Cayce for A.R.E. Congress Sessions], 1977; Folder 27:9
      - report [The Gift: The A.R.E. Library], 1974; Folder 27:9
    - Box 28
      - business cards (2 boxes), 1950 1982; Item 28:1
      - Secret of the Golden Flower materials, 1970 1980; Folder 28:2
    - Box 28A
    - Box 28B
      - address book; task planning, 1971; Folder 28B:1
      - correspondence and receipts [A.R.E. Life Membership Fund], 1965 1974; Folder 28B:2
      - correspondence and receipts [DuPont Glore Forgan Inc.], 1964 1972; Folder 28B:3
      - correspondence and receipts [Edgar Cayce Foundation securities], 1964 1973; Folder 28B:4
      - correspondence and receipts [E.F. Hutton and Company], 1973 1974; Folder 28B:5
      - correspondence and receipts [fire insurance policies], 1971 1974; Folder 28B:6
      - correspondence and receipts [Nationwide Mutual Insurance], 1965 1974; Folder 28B:7
      - correspondence and receipts [Shields and Company], 1965 1975; Folder 28B:8
    - Box 28C
      - general ledger [Prayer and Healing Group; Study Group], 1967 1970; Folder 28C:1
      - payroll [A.R.E.], 1968; Folder 28C:2
      - receipts, September 1955; Folder 28C:3
      - tax returns [A.R.E.], 1946 1970; Folder 28C:4-28C:5
    - Film
      - Box 29
        - contracts [film], 1969 1973; Folder 29:1; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Turner, Gladys Davis; Cayce, Edgar Evans; Edgar Cayce Foundation; Duggan, Pat; Lord, Sterling; Stearn, Jess
        - correspondence [A.R.E. Film Committee], 1973 1974; Folder 29:2; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Main, Murray
        - correspondence [John Beck], 1972; Folder 29:3
        - correspondence [Don Bertram], 1974; Folder 29:4
        - correspondence [Basil Bova and George Vivino] The Edgar Cayce Story, 1961 1972; Folder 29:5-29:6
        - correspondence [film], 1960 1970; Folder 29:7
        - correspondence [film financing], 1976; Folder 29:8
        - correspondence [film promotions], 1971 1972; Folder 29:9
        - corrrespondence [Joel Glickman] Selznick Productions, 1973 1978; Folder 29:10
        - correspondence [Wesley and Alton Ketchum], 1959 1980; Folder 29:11
        - correspondence [Michael Korda], 1963 1966; Folder 29:12
        - correspondence [Allen Landsburg Productions], 1977; Folder 29:13
      - Box 30
        - correspondence [Noel Langley] The Edgar Cayce Story; testimonials from reading recipients, 1961; Folder 30:1; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Langley, Noel; Reilly, Harold J.; Gray, Mamie Butler; Hesson, Sarah Elizabeth Cayce; LeNoir, Ruth; Sumner, Harriet C.; Helms, Mignon; Milholland, Elizabeth; Poss, Peggy; Chandler, Julia; Zentgraf, Helene; Sechrist, Elsie; Morrow, Frances Yelden King; Cayce, Ola; Cayce, Edgar Evans
        - correspondence [Sterling Lord], 1967 1976; Folder 30:2
        - correspondence [Frank Mell], 1974 1976; Folder 30:3
        - correspondence [Chip Miller and Iain Anderson], 1978 1982; Folder 30:4
        - correspondence [Alan Neuman Productions], 1976 1978; Folder 30:5
        - correspondence [research on Edgar Cayce for film projects], 1973 1974; Folder 30:6
        - correspondence [Austin Rice], 1972 1974; Folder 30:7
        - correspondence [San Simeon Corporation], 1971 1973; Folder 30:8
        - correspondence [Milton Sperling Productions], 1968 1971; Folder 30:9-30:10
        - correspondence [Bob Terrio] film on Harold J. Reilly, 1973 1976; Folder 30:11
        - correspondence [Helen Winston], 1968 1972; Folder 30:12
        - correspondence [Loretta Young], 1972 1979; Folder 30:13
    - Newsprint
      - Box 31
        - correspondence [newsprint], 1956 1982; Folder 31:1-31:5
        - correspondence [PM magazine], 1980; Folder 31:6
    - Radio
      - Box 32
        - correspondence [Mel Burka] WTIP-FM, Charleston, West Virginia, 1970 1971; Folder 32:1
        - correspondence [radio station] Station KIEV, Glendale, California, 1963 1964; Folder 32:2
        - correspondence [radio program] The Edgar Cayce Story by Monitor Records, 1959 1961; Folder 32:3
        - correspondence [Tidewater Mysteries radio program], 1961 1966; Folder 32:4
        - proposal [Mysteries of Man radio program], 1966 1970; Folder 32:5
      - Box 33
        - correspondence [Mysteries of the Mind], 1938 1939; Folder 33:1-33:8
      - Box 34
        - correspondence [Mysteries of the Mind], 1938 1939; Folder 34:1-34:5
        - postcards [Mysteries of the Mind], 1938 1939; Folder 34:6
        - story notes [Mysteries of the Mind], 1938 1939; Folder 34:7
        - transcripts [Mysteries of the Mind], 1938 1939; Folder 34:8
      - Box 35
        - correspondence [Mysteries of the Mind], 1938 1939; Folder 35:1-35:5
    - Television
      - Box 32
        - correspondence [Mort Abrams] Suspicion television program, 1957; Folder 32:6
        - correspondence [Jean Claude Roboly], 1978 1980; Folder 32:7
        - correspondence [Jason Phillips] Stories of Success television series, 1969 1970; Folder 32:8
        - correspondence [television viewers], 1971; Folder 32:9
    - Theater
      - Box 32
        - correspondence [Granville Burgess] play, The Freak, 1979 1981; Folder 32:10
        - correspondence [plays about Edgar Cayce], 1961 1968; Folder 32:11
  - Psychic Phenomena, 1939 1982
    - Box 36
      - bibliography [Russian parapsychology research], 1971; Folder 36:1
      - correspondence [Russia tour], 1969 1978; Folder 36:2-36:6
      - newsclippings [Russia tour], 1971; Folder 36:7
      - research notes [Russia tour], undated; Folder 36:8-36:9
      - journal [An Adventure in Russia: The A.R.E. Tour in Parapsychology], 1971; Folder 36:10; Baker, Penny; McGarey, William
    - Box 37
      - booklet [Our Judge and Jury] William N. Petersen, 1951 1961; Folder 37:1A
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] A, 1968 1981; Folder 37:1
      - correspondence [Aron Abrahamsen and Doris Abrahamsen], 1970 1980; Folder 37:2
      - manuscript [Earth Changes], 1973; Folder 37:3
      - newsletters [Aron and Doris Abrahamsen], 1973; Folder 37:4
      - readings [Aron Abrahamsen], 1970 1971; Folder 37:5
      - correspondence [Richard Abrams], 1978 1981; Folder 37:6
      - correspondence [J. Trigg Adams and Margaret Sanders], 1969 1981; Folder 37:7
      - correspondence [John and Louisa Aiken], 1964 1970; Folder 37:8
      - correspondence [Warren Aiken], 1956; Folder 37:9
      - correspondence [Maryann Amadori], 1981; Folder 37:10
      - correspondence [American Society for Psychical Research], 1933 1968; Folder 37:11
      - correspondence [The Arcane Library, United Kingdom], 1964; Folder 37:12
      - correspondence [A.R.E. Psychical Research Laboratory Project], 1961 1963; Folder 37:13-37:14
      - correspondence [A.R.E. Psychical Research Committee], 1968 1986; Folder 37:15
      - correspondence [astrology], 1963 1982; Folder 37:16
    - Box 38
      - correspondence [automatic writing], 1962 1978; Folder 38:1-38:2
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] B, 1960 1980; Folder 38:3
      - correspondence [Clive Backster], 1969; Folder 38:4
      - correspondence [Peter Ballbusch], 1959 1966; Folder 38:5
      - correspondence [Jeanne Barnett], 1965; Folder 38:6
      - correspondence [Barbara Bayly[, 1977 1978; Folder 38:7
      - correspondence [Miriam Belcher], 1939; Folder 38:8
      - correspondence [Samuel Benesch], 1964; Folder 38:9
      - correspondence [Charles Berlitz], 1970 1977; Folder 38:10
      - correspondence [Ethel Berlowe], 1978 1979; Folder 38:11
      - correspondence [Eugene Bernard], 1967; Folder 38:12
      - correspondence [Morey Bernstein], 1952 1978; Folder 38:13
      - correspondence [Samuel Bernstein], 1972 1973; Folder 38:14
      - correspondence [Carolyn Bertrand], 1973 1976; Folder 38:15
      - correspondence [Suzanne Bickel], 1971 1974; Folder 38:16
    - Box 39
      - correspondence [Merry Browne], 1964 1968; Folder 39:1
      - correspondence [David Bubar], 1966 1975; Folder 39:2
      - correspondence [Ken Buck], 1971 1975; Folder 39:3
      - correspondence [Madelyn Came], 1974 1976; Folder 39:4
      - correspondence [Dorris Carlson], 1968 1974; Folder 39:5
      - correspondence [L.N. Chapekar], 1970 1971; Folder 39:6
      - correspondence [Bill Cheb], 1969 1970; Folder 39:7
      - correspondence [Chris Chung], 1979 1980; Folder 39:8
      - correspondence [Jeanne Coffman], 1967 1979; Folder 39:9
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] F, 1959 1972; Folder 39:10
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] I, 1977; Folder 39:11
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] K, 1960 1980; Folder 39:12
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] L, 1957 1981; Folder 39:13
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] N, 1973 1981; Folder 39:14
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] O, 1968; Folder 39:15
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] P, 1964 1979; Folder 39:16
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] S, 1970 1979; Folder 39:17
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] T-V, 1966 1976; Folder 39:18
      - correspondence [communication with Edgar Cayce] W, 1965 1980; Folder 39:19
    - Box 40
      - correspondence [Maggy Conn], 1974 1975; Folder 40:1
      - correspondence [Robert Conner], 1969 1970; Folder 40:2
      - correspondence [Marion Connolly], 1980 1981; Folder 40:3
      - correspondence [Lily Cook], 1969; Folder 40:4
      - correspondence [Mary Cook], 1968; Folder 40:5
      - correspondence [Denny Cooper], 1968 1971; Folder 40:6
      - correspondence [Sterling Cooper-Spencer], 1968 1969; Folder 40:7
      - correspondence [Norma Corrie], 1980 1981; Folder 40:8
      - correspondence [Ruth Crane], 1962; Folder 40:9
      - correspondence [Clarence Cravens], 1962 1963; Folder 40:10
      - correspondence [Bradley Crook], 1974 1975; Folder 40:11
      - correspondence [George Joseph Cross], 1960 1961; Folder 40:12
      - correspondence [Helen Culotta], 1968; Folder 40:13
      - correspondence [Charles Cunningham], 1975 1976; Folder 40:14
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] D, 1976 1980; Folder 40:15
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] DA, 1968 1981; Folder 40:16
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] DE-DI, 1964 1982; Folder 40:17-40:18
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] DO-DY, 1969 1979; Folder 40:19
      - correspondence [Robert Danner], 1974 1981; Folder 40:20
    - Box 41
      - correspondence [Raymond de Gaston], 1977; Folder 41:1
      - correspondence [Martin Dickinson], 1969 1970; Folder 41:2
      - correspondence [Joseph Dillard], 1968 1976; Folder 41:3
      - correspondence [Jeane Dixon], 1963 1970; Folder 41:4-41:6
      - correspondence [Frederick Dommeyer], 1959 1971; Folder 41:7
      - correspondence [Mary Donahue], 1970 1971; Folder 41:8
      - correspondence [Jean Donalson], 1958 1959; Folder 41:9
      - correspondence [Shirley Dorsey], 1983; Folder 41:10
      - correspondence [C.J. Ducasse], 1960 1967; Folder 41:11
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] E, 1964 1981; Folder 41:12
      - correspondence [Harry Emerson], 1958 1960; Folder 41:13
    - Box 42
      - correspondence [Norman Emerson], 1973 1981; Folder 42:1-42:2
      - correspondence [Brent Erickson], 1977 1982; Folder 42:3
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] F, 1969 1976; Folder 42:4
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] F, 1970 1979; Folder 42:5
      - correspondence [Arthur Ford], 1961 1973; Folder 42:6
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] G, 1964 1982; Folder 42:7
      - correspondence [Lyn Garris], 1970 1973; Folder 42:8
      - correspondence [Isaac E. George, Jr.], 1974 1975; Folder 42:9
      - correspondence [Karen Getsla], 1976; Folder 42:10
      - correspondence [Harry Glover], 1968 1973; Folder 42:11
      - correspondence [Jeffrey Goodman], 1970 1977; Folder 42:12
    - Box 43
      - correspondence [Stephen Goranson], 1975 1982; Folder 43:1
      - correspondence [Bernard Grad], 1964 1968; Folder 43:2
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] H, 1966 1981; Folder 43:3-43:4
      - correspondence [Clayton and Mary Haake], 1975 1977; Folder 43:5-43:6
      - correspondence [Andy Kerl Hagenweg], 1981; Folder 43:7
      - correspondence [J. Haliburton], 1970 1982; Folder 43:8
      - correspondence [Lalsingh Harribance], 1971 1980; Folder 43:9
      - correspondence [Shirley Hatcher], 1959; Folder 43:10
      - correspondence [Margaret Holtman], 1969 1979; Folder 43:11
    - Box 44
      - correspondence [Margaret Holtman], 1969 1979; Folder 44:1
      - correspondence [Hans Holzer], 1960 1978; Folder 44:2
      - correspondence [Charles and Kay Hoselton], 1975 1981; Folder 44:3
      - correspondence [Peter Hurkos], 1959 1961; Folder 44:4
      - correspondence [Joseph Jahoda], 1964 1982; Folder 44:5
      - correspondence [Franklin Loehr], 1951 1970; Folder 44:6
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] M, 1974 1975; Folder 44:7
      - correspondence [Ken MacIver], 1969 1977; Folder 44:8
      - correspondence [Betty McCain], 1958 1979; Folder 44:9-44:12
      - correspondence [Walter McGraw], 1960 1968; Folder 44:13
      - correspondence [George McMullen], 1975 1981; Folder 44:14
    - Box 45
      - correspondence [George McMullen], 2005 2007; Folder 45:1
      - correspondence [George McMullen] psychometry reports, Iran, 1975; Folder 45:2
      - correspondence [George McMullen] psychometry reports, Israel, 1977; Folder 45:3
      - correspondence [Ruth Montgomery], 1963 1978; Folder 45:4-45:7
      - correspondence [Thelma Moss], 1970 1976; Folder 45:8
      - correspondence [Gardner Murphy], 1937 1948; Folder 45:9
      - correspondence [Joseph Myers], 1962 1982; Folder 45:10-45:12
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] N, 1971 1980; Folder 45:13
      - correspondence [Nicholas Nestor], 1960 1962; Folder 45:14
    - Box 46
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] O, 1968 1981; Folder 46:1
      - correspondence [George O'Malley], 1961 1981; Folder 46:2
      - correspondence [Raymond C. Owens], 1963 1981; Folder 46:3
      - correspondence [Ted Owens], 1964 1978; Folder 46:4-46:6
      - correspondence [past lives], 1961 1981; Folder 46:7
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] P, 1951 1978; Folder 46:8-46:9
      - correspondence [Byron Pace], 1964 1965; Folder 46:10
      - correspondence [Antonio Perdiz], 1970 1981; Folder 46:11
      - correspondence [Ross Peterson], 1976 1981; Folder 46:12
      - correspondence [Susan Pfeffer], 1978 1979; Folder 46:13
      - correspondence [Dorothy Frances Phillips], 1967; Folder 46:14
    - Box 47
      - correspondence [Ruth Porter], 1959 1961; Folder 47:1
      - correspondence [Geneva Potell], 1975; Folder 47:2
      - correspondence [J. Gaither Pratt], 1964 1975; Folder 47:3
      - correspondence [Alfred W. Price], 1958 1968; Folder 47:4
      - correspondence [prophecy], 1962 1981; Folder 47:5-47:8
      - correspondence [psychic claims of Edgar Cayce's handwriting], 1971 1979; Folder 47:9
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] R, 1968 1982; Folder 47:10-47:11
      - correspondence [Larry Riddle], 1970; Folder 47:12
      - correspondence [Peter Riddle], 1974 1980; Folder 47:13
    - Box 48
      - correspondence [Samuel Rizzo], 1963 1977; Folder 48:1
      - correspondence [William G. Roll], 1964 1977; Folder 48:2
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] S, 1956 1982; Folder 48:3-48:8
      - correspondence [Edward Snedeker], 1971 1979; Folder 48:9
    - Box 49
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] T, 1968 1982; Folder 49:1
      - correspondence [Joy Talley], 1963 1969; Folder 49:2
      - correspondence [Charles T. Tart], 1957 1969; Folder 49:3
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] U, 1969; Folder 49:4
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] V, 1979 1980; Folder 49:5
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] W, 1957 1981; Folder 49:6
      - correspondence [psychic phenomena] Z, 1979 1980; Folder 49:7
    - Box 50
      - binder [Project X] 9T6, 1955 1956; Folder 50:1-50:2
      - #1, Project X notes, 1951; Folder 50:3
      - #2, Project X notes, 1951; Folder 50:4
      - #3, Project X notes, 1950 1951; Folder 50:5
      - #4, Project X notes, 1950 1951; Folder 50:6
      - #5, Project X notes, 1950 1951; Folder 50:7
      - #6, Project X notes, 1950 1951; Folder 50:8
      - #7, Project X notes, 1950 1951; Folder 50:9
    - Box 51
      - binder [Project X] A20, 1955 1956; Folder 51:1
      - binder [Project X] B-16; BQ5; 3Q6; 66Q; 63-R; tQ4, 1955 1956; Folder 51:2
      - binder [Project X] 9T6, 1956; Folder 51:3
      - binder [Project X] Project Results, Forms, Questionnaires, 1956; Folder 51:4
      - supplemental material, Project X, 1951 2013; Folder 51:5
  - Publishing, 1945 1981
    - Box 52
      - A.R.E. booklet research materials [Cases in Reincarnation], 1959; Folder 52:1
      - correspondence [Bantam Books], 1969 1975; Folder 52:2
      - correspondence [Coronet Magazine], 1967 1970; Folder 52:3
      - correspondence [Coward-McCann, Inc., Publishers], 1969 1972; Folder 52:4
      - correspondence [Dell Publishing Company], 1963 1981; Folder 52:5
      - correspondence [Doubleday and Company] My Life with Edgar Cayce, 1962 1972; Folder 52:6
      - correspondence [Edgar Cayce's Photographic Legacy], 1975 1978; Folder 52:7
      - correspondence [Fate Magazine], 1968 1979; Folder 52:8
      - correspondence [Fawcett Publications] Edgar Cayce: Mystery Man of Miracles, 1956 1969; Folder 52:9
      - correspondence [Harper and Row, Publishers], 1964 1979; Folder 52:10
      - correspondence [Harper and Row, Publishers] Faces of Fear, 1977 1981; Folder 52:11
      - correspondence [Harper Brothers], 1953 1957; Folder 52:12
      - correspondence [Hawthorn Books], 1967 1970; Folder 52:13
      - correspondence [Henry Holt and Company] film rights for There Is A River, 1954 1981; Folder 52:14
      - correspondence [Hudson Publishing Company], 1970; Folder 52:15
      - correspondence [Kent Publishing Company], 1954 1956; Folder 52:16